<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Minutes on Black Mirror: Hated in the Nation</title>
    <link>https://dfontana.github.io/socialimps/minutes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Minutes on Black Mirror: Hated in the Nation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dfontana.github.io/socialimps/minutes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation Refining</title>
      <link>https://dfontana.github.io/socialimps/minutes/meeting4_27/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dfontana.github.io/socialimps/minutes/meeting4_27/</guid>
      <description>Actions Completed  Checked in on site updates to make sure everything was accounted for Reviewed what everyone had drafted, making edits to individual slides to make sure the arguments flowed well. Also made sure context was being provided for each argument presented. Adjusted a few of the visual elements.  Assigned Tasks  Dylan: Send out When2Meet on Saturday to find a time for rehearsing Everyone: Practice slides to make sure you are ready.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation Drafting</title>
      <link>https://dfontana.github.io/socialimps/minutes/meeting4_20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dfontana.github.io/socialimps/minutes/meeting4_20/</guid>
      <description> Actions Completed  Discussed the site updates Discussed powerpoint topics/outline/plan Created template of powerpoint  Assigned Tasks Topic Posts (Completed by today / nearly done)  Sam: Dividing chapter 9 related info to chapter 8 and 10 posts Synella: Writing chapter 10 post Dylan: Writing chapter 8 post Adam: Outline initial ideas of powerpoint  Presentation  Ming: Slides 1&amp;frasl;2 (Summary &amp;amp; Outline) Adam: Slide 7 (Surveillance) Synella: Slide 5 (Online Responsibility) Sam: Slide 4 (Maker&amp;rsquo;s Intent) Dylan: Slide 6 (Trust in Autonomous items)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Initial Meeting</title>
      <link>https://dfontana.github.io/socialimps/minutes/meeting4_8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dfontana.github.io/socialimps/minutes/meeting4_8/</guid>
      <description>Actions Completed  Caught up with one another on the show Listed topics up to Tuesday.  Discussed which were relevant (All but IP)  Divvy&amp;rsquo;d Tasks for Tuesday  Assigned Tasks Topic Posts Take the topic from class and the relevant chapter from the book. Talk about how it relates to the movie as much as possible, critically looking at what the movie may be trying to say, and the implications of what it has to present.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>