<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Topics on Black Mirror: Hated in the Nation</title>
    <link>https://dfontana.github.io/socialimps/topics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Topics on Black Mirror: Hated in the Nation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dfontana.github.io/socialimps/topics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Intellectual Property</title>
      <link>https://dfontana.github.io/socialimps/topics/intellectualproperty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dfontana.github.io/socialimps/topics/intellectualproperty/</guid>
      <description>As we covered in class, and the text, Intellectual Property is mostly concerned with ownership of a creation/idea - be it through Copyright, Patents, or Trade Secret. In our movie, the matter at hand is a crisis in social media coupled with cybercrime, privacy, and freedom of speech. As such, this topic is not truly relevant to Black Mirror: Hated in the Nation, as the conflict pursued by the film centers on these other issues it finds more pressing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dfontana.github.io/socialimps/topics/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dfontana.github.io/socialimps/topics/privacy/</guid>
      <description>+++ date = &amp;ldquo;2018-04-10&amp;rdquo; draft = false title = &amp;ldquo;Privacy&amp;rdquo; author = &amp;ldquo;Ming&amp;rdquo;
categories = [&amp;ldquo;Topics&amp;rdquo;] weight = 2 type = &amp;ldquo;post&amp;rdquo; +++
Privacy in Black Mirror: Hated in the Nation The TV series Black Mirror covers different topics in each episode, including security, data science and robotics. Black Mirror: Hated in the Nation, which is the last episode of this TV series, talks about a controversial topic — privacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dfontana.github.io/socialimps/topics/crime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dfontana.github.io/socialimps/topics/crime/</guid>
      <description>+++ date = &amp;ldquo;2018-04-10&amp;rdquo; draft = false title = &amp;ldquo;Crime&amp;rdquo; author = &amp;ldquo;Adam&amp;rdquo;
categories = [&amp;ldquo;Topics&amp;rdquo;] weight = 2 type = &amp;ldquo;post&amp;rdquo; +++
Crime in Black Mirror: Hated in the Nation In chapter 7 of the textbook, there is a section on hacking that contains a case study about the Firefox extension, Firesheep. The extension, launched in 2010, makes sidejacking easy, even for people without a technical understanding of what they are actually doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dfontana.github.io/socialimps/topics/freedomofspeech/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dfontana.github.io/socialimps/topics/freedomofspeech/</guid>
      <description>Freedom of Speech in Black Mirror: Hated in the Nation The topic of Freedom of Speech is heavily critiqued in this episode of the British anthology series, Black Mirror. The crux of this episode revolves around a social media hashtag #deathto. The original intent of this hashtag was for every day users of this social media site to express their feelings towards a particular individual. This seems harmless at first - in the United States of America, the First Amendment protects the citizens&amp;rsquo; right to freedom of speech.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>